if you're going to do
如果你要做
it do
这样做
it say what you can do do what you say
它说你能做什么你说的
if you can't do it don't say you can do
如果你不能这样做，不要说你可以做
it don't over leverage yourself don't
它不会过度利用自己不要
over leverage the decision and then jump
过度利用决定然后跳跃
in and kind of dip a toe I think I'll
我想我会
try it out no think if you're going to
尝试一下，不要想你是否要
try it out beforehand but when it's time
事先尝试一下，但是时间
to go dive finish it find out come out
要进行潜水，发现出来了
the other side don't leave it and
另一边不留下它，
go if I just would it uh-uh that keeps
如果我愿意的话，请继续
me up at night I think it keeps a lot of
我晚上起床，我认为它保留了很多
us up at night when you half ass
晚上你一半屁股时我们起来
something you just don't know whether
你只是不知道是否
you failed or succeeded got what you
你失败或成功得到了你
want or didn't get what you want finding
想要或没有得到想要找到的东西
out and looking in the mirror and going
外面看镜子，然后去
I didn't have HD I went all the way I
我没有高清我一路走了
found out and that ain't for me or I
发现了，这不是我或我
found out and you damn right that is for
发现了，你该死的是
me that's a great place to get
我是一个好地方
to I think part of the challenges in
我认为一部分挑战
life is a lot of us are running around
生活是我们很多人正在奔波
half assing ourselves half foing
一半屁股
ourselves not full of ourselves not
我们自己不是充满自己的
studying ourselves enough not holding
学习足够的不举行
oursel to task enough not patting our
我们的任务足以不拍我们
own self on the back when we do get what
当我们得到什么时，自己的自我
we want enough not cracking our own whip
我们想要足够的不破解自己的鞭子
on our backside when we do get out of
当我们离开时，在我们的背面
line even though we knew better I wish
线，即使我们希望更好
we were more full of ourselves that
我们更充满自己
way someone said this to me before
有人以前对我这么说
Matthew you're so full of yourself and I
马修，你是如此充满自己，我
that thinking I was like well who else
那个想我很好
am I supposed to be full
我应该饱满吗
of that's a good line and I stopped
这是一个很好的路线，我停了下来
after I was like that's exactly what I
在我就像那之后，我正是我
meant I went wrote that down I wish more
意味着我去写下来，我希望更多
people were more full of themselves
人们更充满自己
I think we should take some time to be
我认为我们应该花一些时间
able to look in the mirror and own that
能够照镜子并拥有
thing that we pulled off and
我们拉下的东西
go good job that's what you wanted it's
做得好，这就是你想要的
what you
你什么
got at the same time be able to as we do
同时能够像我们一样
more often look in the mirror when we
当我们
fail and go uh-uh bogey you not pull
失败，去柏忌，你不要拉
that
那
off give others and yourself more credit
离开给别人和你自己更多的信用
happiness you can't guarantee it but
幸福你不能保证，但是
there is a science to satisfaction there
那里有一门科学要满足
you can look at habits that
您可以看一下习惯
engineered less pain in your life maybe
在您的生活中减少痛苦也许
more pleasure but at least less pain and
更快乐，但至少减轻了痛苦和
that's that's a
那就是一个
win so much easier to be supportive and
赢得支持和支持
gentle of other people than of ourselves
别人的温柔
you know you will happily bestow this
你知道你会很高兴地赐予
sort of gentle
有点温柔
reassuring pat on the shoulder when
放心，当
somebody succeeds or falls short when
有人成功或跌倒
they tried their best yet given the fact
鉴于事实，他们尽了最大的努力
that you tried your best you give
你尽力而为
yourself a kick on the way out of the
您自己踢出了
door and a harsh word to follow you yep
门和一个苛刻的词跟随你是的
because I got myself in the pickle cuz
因为我把自己放在泡菜里
things didn't go how I wanted it to go
事情没有去做我想要的
or how I believed it could
或我如何相信它可以
go life's the ironic tragedy life is
去生活是讽刺的悲剧生活
pain I'm the reason that I stepped in
痛苦我是我介入的原因
which is also an asset even if someone
即使有人
go you why are you giving yourself so
去你为什么要给自己
much credit for screwing that
搞砸了
up we're going to make mistakes
我们要犯错
you got to own them then you got to make
你必须拥有它们，然后你必须做
amends and then you got to move on guilt
修改，然后你要犯罪
and regret kills many a man before their
后悔在他们之前杀死了许多男人
time so turn the page get off the ride
时间，请将页面下车骑行
you are the author of the book of your
您是您的书的作者
[Music]
[音乐]
life there are habits that I notice of
我注意到的生活习惯
things I take care of in my life
我一生中照顾的事情
healthwise Faith Wise father- Wise
健康信仰明智
husband wise if I'm doing that
丈夫明智的话，如果我这样做
consistently there's less value
一贯的价值
the ironic tragedy is that life has to
具有讽刺意味的悲剧是生活必须
be lived forward but only makes sense in
生活在前进，但只有有意义
Reverse when you look back we we can all
当您回头时，我们都可以
connect every single dot it's
连接每个点
mathematical scientific how we got to
数学科学我们如何去
this table right here it's it's it's all
这张桌子就在这里
connected if we go back and look at it
如果我们回去看它，请连接
and there's a whole lot of I thought
我想
that was the end well it was the end but
那是最后的结局，但是
it was the beginning of this
这是这个开始
thing what you're leaning into is that
您倾向于的是
mystery going forward right that ironic
讽刺的是神秘
CH that you have something to push off
CH，您有什么要推开的
the well I don't know what I do want but
我不知道我想要什么，但是
I do know I don't want that you have
我确实知道我不想你有
leverage yes you know to it's it's
利用是的，你知道是
there you know we always say well who
在那里你知道我们总是说谁
are you you I want you figure out who
你是你我想知道谁
you are and we ask I tried to I try not
你是，我们问我尝试我不尝试
to ask my kids that now well I want you
问我的孩子，现在我要你
to know who you are now part of that
知道您现在是谁
who's helped me is Bob Dylan L like I
谁帮助我是鲍勃·迪伦（Bob Dylan L）
don't know what all this talks about who
不知道这一切谈论谁
we are man we are all just what we
我们是男人，我们都是我们的
create ourselves to be and that gives me
创造自己的生命，这给了我
a little oh that's relaxing but the it's
有点哦，这很放松，但是
so much easier to figure out who you're
这么容易弄清楚你是谁
not and if you start eliminating the who
不是，如果您开始消除谁
I'm not by sheer mathematics you end up
我不是纯粹的数学你最终
moving toward who more of what feeds you
朝着谁养活你的人迈进
and who you are and it's a hell of a lot
你是谁，这真是太多了
easier thing to go how can I get rid of
更容易去做的事情如何摆脱
some in my life than it is to
我生活中的一些
go well how do I go to my true
走得很好，我该如何实现
[Music]
[音乐]
self do I want to press the accelerator
我想按加速器
more quickly or do I want to take my
更快或我想带我
foot off the break
踏上休息
sometimes the hard work and the
有时辛勤的工作和
endurance and the elbow grease the work
耐力和肘部润滑脂
harder we were talking about that hustle
我们更努力地谈论那个喧嚣
is not the way out sometimes it's I need
有时候不是出路，我需要
to back up laugh have a sip of my
支持笑声让我sip
favorite whatever and dance my way
最喜欢的什么，跳舞我的方式
through the raindrops out of this
通过雨滴
Su and even looking at the things that
su，甚至看的东西
are bad and
很糟糕
going oh thank you appreciate
哦，谢谢你感谢
that I think one of the themes of your
我认为您的主题之一
worldview that I've become familiar with
我熟悉的世界观
is alchemizing bad times into good ones
炼金术时期的糟糕时期
a reminder that things that seem bad can
提醒您的事情看起来很糟糕
end up being good how can people or how
最终变得很好，如何或如何
do you have more of that perspective
你有更多的观点吗
during a hard
在艰难的过程中
time I probably start off
我可能开始的时间
intellectualizing something that I know
使我知道的事物进行智力化
I probably should believe in but don't
我可能应该相信，但不要
believe in it and convince myself even
相信它，甚至说服自己
to an extent to trick my
在某种程度上欺骗了我
myself that you know to sit here and go
我自己知道坐在这里去
well you just tell yourself this two
好吧，你只是告诉自己这两个
Shall Pass okay great well what the
可以通过
hell's that mean even if it's true in
地狱意味着即使在
the moment you're like what are youing
当你就像你在你的那一刻
talking about man I'm in the debit
谈论男人，我在借方
section I'm in I'm I'm I'm in a warning
部分我在里面我是警告
section I'm I'm it this this
部分是我这个
sucks I I think that how much I'm
很烂，我想我有多
conscious of it or not my undeniable
意识到它是否不可否认
optimism in faith
对信仰的乐观主义
that this isn't all it is and if it is
这不是全部，如果是
oh so what that that that's okay well
哦，那没关系
then really so what you know what I mean
那真是你知道我的意思
what's the big deal it minimizes I don't
最小的我不这样做是什么大不了的
I I seem to have a tendency not to make
我似乎有不做的趋势
a bigger deal out of things
从事更大的事情
that other people make a bigger deal of
其他人做了更大的
Dramas I don't like to create false
戏剧，我不喜欢创建错误
drama when it comes into its hard I am
戏剧时，我很难
affected I I I I I get the blues I get
受影响的我我我我得到了我得到的蓝调
sad I get mad I'm a the be around I
难过我生气我是我周围的
can't get to sleep I got demons in my
无法入睡，我有恶魔
own head trying to work trying to work
自己的头试图工作
the riddle out why did this happen
谜语为什么会发生这种情况
that's the other thing that's tough for
那是另一件事很难
me is I think that any bad thing that
我认为那是什么坏事
happens to me my initial reaction is
发生在我身上我的最初反应是
what' you do wrong to to lead to
你做错了什么
this heard a quote recently that said
最近听到了一句话
every man knows reflection and
每个人都知道反思和
introspection when he's at his lowest
当他处于最低水平时内省
bad times you can't do anything other
糟糕的时光你不能做其他任何事情
than wallow in retrospective
比回顾性
assessments uh but one of my favorite
评估呃，但我最喜欢的
things I've learned from you is when
我从你那里学到的东西是什么时候
things are going well given that that's
鉴于那是
presumably what you want to have more of
大概您想拥有更多
may be worth deconstructing that yes can
可能是值得解构的，是的
I B can I try and bottle some science
我可以尝试瓶装一些科学吗
here to why things are going well and I
在这里，为什么事情进展顺利，我
did find consistencies you were
确实找到了你的一致性
appreciating more you were pointing out
感谢您指出的更多
beautiful things and not taking them for
美丽的事物，不带它们
granted and so I found a list of things
理所当然，所以我找到了一份清单
I'm like and when I get off track I try
我喜欢，当我脱离轨道时，我会尝试
to remind myself ah you've been slacking
提醒自己啊，你一直在懈怠
on some of those I've definitely found
在我肯定发现的一些
consistencies and I think we all have
一致性，我认为我们都有
them if we just notate them along the
如果我们只是在
way that they're not by
他们不在的方式
accident let's cheers let's a teers on
事故让我们加油吧，让我们开心
the way for all the things that are work
所有工作事物的方式
for when we have going right also
因为当我们走了
knowing that it's not forever that it
知道这不是永远的
will we will have a mountain to climb
我们将有一座山要爬吗
here
这里
shortly what's my best advice I need to
不久，我需要什么最好的建议
give myself right now is listen to my
现在给自己是听我的
own damn
自己该死
[Laughter]
[笑声]
advice now we used to look up in the sky
建议现在我们曾经在天空中抬头
and wonder at our place in the stars I
想知道我在星空中的位置
want to skip the flattery and the adab
想跳过奉承和adab
boys cuz I do know
男孩，因为我知道
this the sooner that we become less
这越早变得越来越少
impressed with our life with our
对我们的生活印象深刻
accomplishments with our career with
与我们的职业成就
whatever that Prospect is in front of us
无论我们面前的前景如何
the sooner we become less impressed and
我们越早留下深刻的印象，
more involved with that and these
更多地参与了这些
things the sooner we get a whole lot
事情越早得到很多
better at doing them it's like we
更好地做它们就像我们
forgotten who we are at home explorers
忘记了我们在家的探险家
Pioneers not caretakers now why do you
先驱者现在不是看护人
pursue things that scare you why seek
追求吓yo的事情为什么寻找
the role that's hard because it cost me
很难的角色，因为它使我付出了代价
something cuz it cost it comes with a
因为它花费的东西带有一个
price it's not really a risk unless you
价格除非您
can lose the fight I feel more alive in
可以失去我感到更活跃的战斗
them I have an experience in the making
他们我有经验
of them I'm nervous every day I come to
我每天都会紧张
work I he the things you can get away
工作，我可以逃脱的东西
with in this world everything you can't
在这个世界上，一切都不能
life is not easy it is not don't try to
生活并不容易，不是不尝试
make it that way life's not fair it
这样使生活不公平
never was it isn't now and it won't ever
从来都不是现在，永远不会
be do not fall into the Trap the
不要陷入陷阱
entitlement trap of feeling like you're
权利的陷阱就像你
a victim you are not get over it and get
受害者，您没有克服它并获得
on with it and yes most things are more
在它上面，是的，大多数事情都更多
rewarding when you break a sweat to get
当您汗流以获取时，有意义
them I feel like when I nail a day and I
他们觉得当我每天钉时，我
knock it and I know I did I feel like
敲打它，我知道我觉得
yes I get I I have a measure at the end
是的，我得到了我最后的措施
of the day like you set out to do
就像您打算做的那一天
something you prepared for it you had
您为它准备的东西
intention and you did it that gives me
意图，你做到了
gratification that makes me feel gives
使我感到的满足
me significance that gives me confidence
我的意义使我有信心
so be brave have courage and when you do
所以要勇敢勇敢，当你做的时候
you get stronger you get more aware you
你变得更强大，你会更加意识到你
get more respectful of
更加尊重
yourself and that which you fear want to
你自己和你害怕想要的
talk about our opponent this afternoon
今天下午谈论我们的对手
you're bigger faster stronger more
您更大的速度更强壮
experienced and on paper they're just
经验丰富，在纸上他们只是
better and they know it
更好，他们知道
too but I want to tell you something
我也想告诉你一些事情
that they don't
他们没有
know they don't know your heart
知道他们不知道你的心
what cuz heading out there is what I
什么是我的
feel like I was born to
感觉我是天生的
do and it excites
这样做很兴奋
me oh just because you can nah come on
我哦，只是因为你不能来
it's not a good enough reason to do
这不是足够的理由
something even when it means having
即使这意味着
more be Discerning choose it because you
更多辨别力选择，因为您
want it do it because you want
想要这样做，因为你想要
to it's on you
对你在你身上
it's on
它正在打开
[Music]
[音乐]
you we remember the stuff we earn the
你我们记得我们赚到的东西
stuff we experience more than what the
我们经历的东西比什么
teacher tells us or what someone gives
老师告诉我们或有人给
us for free we just do we broke a
我们免费，我们只是打破了
proverbial sweat on it whether it was
不管是
mental or physical or whatever we we we
身心
we built it we we understand we felt how
我们构建了它，我们知道我们感觉到
we got it how we achieved it how we got
我们明白了我们如何实现的方式
what we
我们什么
wanted those stick with us whether we
想要那些与我们一起坚持
forget them intellectual they were
忘记他们的知识分子
written in our lineage and they build
写在我们的血统中，他们建立
resilience and they and and and they
弹性，他们和他们
build a healthy true optimism going
建立健康的真正乐观
forward to know that oh no i' I've I've
回头知道哦，我'我已经
worked for something before and achieved
以前工作并取得了成就
it delayed gratification oh there are
它推迟满足哦，有
choices I can make today for myself that
我今天可以做出的选择
will pay me back later in
稍后会付给我
life and I've Got Friends and trust me
生活，我有朋友，相信我
I've done it myself you know that lose a
我自己做了，你知道失去了
job and then get another but won't take
工作，然后得到另一个，但不会接受
it cuz it's less salary than maybe the
因为它的薪水比
one they had before and all of a sudden
他们以前有一个突然
find themselves 3 4 5 6 7 8 years a
发现自己3 4 5 6 7 8年A
decade later going they're still stuck
十年后，他们仍然被困
they they didn't do anything they're
他们什么都没做
still saying like no I'm going to find
仍然说不，我会找到
that thing and I'm going like you missed
那东西，我要你想念的
a decade man just go do that one that
一个十年的人去做那个
that you love to do that maybe was going
你喜欢这样做，也许正在去
to pay you less because you'd at least
少付钱，因为你至少会
been building something through the day
整天都在建造东西
and who knows what that would have led
谁知道那会带来什么
to maybe that would have led to
也许那会导致
something where you're getting paid five
您得到五个的东西
times more than you were doing something
次比你做某事还要多
else you love even more uh so sometimes
否则你更爱嗯，有时
it's not even about what choice we make
甚至不是我们做出的选择
just make a choice and commit to it and
只是做出选择并承诺，
go and dive in
去潜水
mhm M so while we're here and they're
MHM M，所以我们在这里，他们
going to run across the Jumbo Tron let's
要穿过巨型特隆
make it a place where we break a
使它成为我们破裂的地方
sweat where we believe where we enjoy
汗水我们相信我们喜欢的地方
the process of succeeding in the places
在这些地方取得成功的过程
and ways that we are fashioned to where
以及我们被塑造的方式
we don't have to look over our shoulder
我们不必看着我们的肩膀
because we're too busy doing what we're
因为我们太忙于做我们的事情
good at voluntarily keeping our own
擅长自愿保持自己的
Council because we want to traveling
理事会是因为我们想旅行
towards Immortal Finish Lines we write
迈向不朽的终点线我们写
our own book overcoming our fears we
我们自己的书克服了我们的恐惧
make friends with ourselves and that is
与自己交朋友，那就是
the
这
place that I'm talking
我说话的地方
about from the soles of your feet with
大约从你的脚脚底
every ounce of blood you've got in your
你在你里面得到的每一盎司的血液
body lay it on the line until the final
身体放在线上直到决赛
whistle blows and if you do
吹口哨，如果你这样做
[Music]
[音乐]
that if you do
如果你这样做
that we cannot not
我们不能
lose so turn the page get off the ride
丢失，请转到页面下车
you are the author of the book of your
您是您的书的作者
life knowing who we are is
生活知道我们是谁
hard it's hard give yourself a break
很难让自己休息一下
eliminate who you are not first and
消除你不是第一位的人
you're going to find yourself where you
你要找到自己的地方
need to
需要
be and the Oscar goes
是和奥斯卡
to Matthew mccon I had a very important
对马修·麦康（Matthew McCon），我有一个非常重要的
person in my life come to me and say
我一生中的人来找我说
who's your hero and I said I don't know
谁是你的英雄，我说我不知道
I got to think about that give me a
我必须考虑一下给我一个
couple of weeks I come back two weeks
几周我回来了两个星期
later this person comes up and says
后来这个人出现了
who's your hero I said I thought about
我说我是谁的英雄
it you know who it is I said it's me in
你知道我是谁，我说是我
years so I turned 25 10 years later that
几年所以我25岁，十年后
same person comes to me and goes so are
同一个人来找我，去了
you're a hero and I was like not even
你是英雄，我什至没有
close no no no she said why I said
关闭不，不，她说我为什么说
because my hero is me at 35 so you see
因为我的英雄是我35岁，所以你看到
every day every week every month and
每个月的每一天，
every year of my
我的每一年
life my hero is always 10 years away I'm
生活我的英雄总是十年了
never going to be my hero I'm not going
永远不会成为我的英雄，我不会去
to attain that I know I'm not and that's
为了达到我知道我不是，那就是
just fine with me cuz that keeps me with
很好，因为让我保持
somebody to keep on
有人继续
chasing so to any of us whatever those
无论那些那些那些
things are whatever it is we look up to
一切都是我们仰望的一切
whatever it is we look forward to and
无论我们期待什么
whoever it is we're chasing to that I
无论是谁，我们都在追赶我
say Amen to that I say all right all
说阿们，我说得很好
right all
一切
right that I say just keep living huh
是的，我说继续生活
thank
感谢
you nobody has ever choked I have huh
你没人cho住我
you know what I'm talking about fumbling
你知道我在说什么
at the goal line stuck your foot in your
在进球线上
mouth once you got to the microphone Had
一旦你到达麦克风
a Brain Freeze on the exam that you were
大脑在考试中冻结
totally prepared for forgot the
完全为忘记
punchline to a joke in front of 4,000
在4,000的面前开个玩笑
graduating students at the University of
大学的学生
Houston
休斯顿
commencement or maybe you've had that
开始或也许你有
feeling of oh my God life just cannot
哦，我的上帝的生活根本无法
get any better than this moment and ask
比这一刻更好，问
yourself do I deserve this now what
我自己现在应该得到这个
happens when we get that feeling
当我们得到那种感觉时会发生
tense up we have this sort of outer body
紧张，我们有这种外部身体
experience where we are literally seeing
我们从字面上看到的经验
oursel in the third person and we
我们的第三人称和我们
realize that the moment just got bigger
意识到那一刻越来越大
than us you ever felt that
比我们曾经觉得
way I
我的路
have and it's because we have created a
有，这是因为我们创建了一个
fictitious ceiling a roof to our
虚拟的天花板向我们的屋顶
expectations of
期望
ourselves a limit where we think think
我们自己认为的一个极限
it's all too good to be
一切都太好了
true but it's
是的，但这是
not and it's not our right to say or
不是，这不是我们说的权利或
believe it
相信它
is we shouldn't create these
我们不应该创建这些吗
restrictions on ourselves a blue ribbon
对自己的限制蓝丝带
a statue a score a great idea the love
一个雕像得分一个好主意
of our life a euphoric Bliss who are we
我们的生活是一个欣喜的幸福
that think that we don't deserve or
认为我们不应该得到或
haven't earned these gifts when we get
当我们得到的时候还没有赚到这些礼物
them it's not our
他们不是我们的
right but if we stay in process all
是的，但是如果我们待在整个过程中
right within ourselves in the joy of the
就在我们内心的喜悦中
doing we will never choke at the Finish
这样做我们永远不会扼杀
Line why because we aren't thinking of
为什么为什么我们不考虑
the Finish Line cuz we're not looking at
终点线，因为我们不在寻找
the clock we're not watching ourselves
时钟我们没有看着自己
on the Jumbotron performing The Very act
在Jumbotron上执行的行为
that we're in the middle of no we're in
我们处在我们中间
process the approach is the destination
处理方法是目的地
and we are never finished Bo Jackson
而且我们从来没有完成Bo Jackson
what do you do he used to run over the
你用来做什么
goal line through the end zone and up
通过末端区域及向上的球门线
the tunnel the greatest snipers and and
隧道最大的狙击手和
marksmen in the world they don't aim at
他们没有瞄准的世界上的射手
the Target they aim on the other side of
他们针对的目标
the
这
target we do our best when our
目标我们在我们的
destinations are beyond the measurement
目的地超出了测量
when our reach continually exceeds our
当我们的影响力不断超过我们
grasp and when we have Immortal Finish
掌握，当我们有不朽的饰面
Lines and when we do this the race is
线路，当我们这样做时，比赛是
never over the journey has no Port the
从来没有旅途中没有端口
adventure never ends because we are
冒险永远不会结束，因为我们是
always on the way so do this do this and
总是在路上这样做，这样做
let them let somebody else come up and
让他们让别人出现
tap you on the shoulder and say Hey you
敲你肩膀说嘿，你
schooler let them run up and tap you on
学生让他们跑起来，然后点击你
the shoulder and say man you want let
肩膀，说你想要的
them come tell you you can go home now
他们来告诉你你现在可以回家
let them say I love you
让他们说我爱你
too let them say thank you take the lid
他们也让他们说谢谢你盖上盖子
off the man-made roofs that we put above
从我们放在上面的人造屋顶上
ourselves and always play like an
我们自己，总是像一个
underdog
失败者
here we
我们在这里
[Applause]
[掌声]
go um responsibility of freedom and the
承担自由的责任和
freedom in responsibility life's more
责任自由生活更多
than just straight Saturdays with as
不仅仅是周六
much cake as you want to eat it just is
你想吃的蛋糕很多
you will see how long you last doing
你会看到你上次做的时间
that if you really do it you won't last
如果您真的这样做，您将不会持续
that long responsibility is is
长期的责任是
appreciation of a past it's building of
对过去的欣赏是建立的
a lineage it's investing in ourselves
它正在对自己进行投资的血统
it's investing in something we started
它正在投资我们开始的东西
to build yesterday that we want to take
昨天建造我们要采取的
into tomorrow there's a respon that
明天有一个响应
gives us freedom so to actually have
给我们的自由，所以实际拥有
true Freedom we have to be more
真正的自由我们必须更多
responsible for certain things for
负责某些事情
ourselves who we are constantly
我们自己一直是谁
investigating and interrogating our
调查和询问我们的
better selves to say I'm going to be a
更好地说我将成为一个
little bit better at this tomorrow
明天好一点
knowing that we Never Land we never we
知道我们永远不会着陆我们永远不会
never there's no there's no taada moment
从来没有没有塔达的时刻
and that is one thing I think we all got
这是我认为我们都得到的一件事
to watch CU we all are so result
要观看cu，我们都是如此结果
oriented but there's no cha moment we're
面向但没有Cha时刻
always chasing yet and if we can get
总是追逐，如果我们能得到
comfortable and understand and laugh at
舒适，理解和笑
and and and be ready to work hard at the
并准备在
fact that we're all just achieving our
事实，我们都在实现我们的
way to the unachievable and that's as
进入无法实现的方式，那就是
good as it gets and that's pretty damn
不错，那真是该死
awesome thank you good
太棒了谢谢你
luck just keep living
运气只是继续生活
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]